This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander.
A hero.
This is my story!
Oh, oh,
oh,
oh.
That's why we all meet us.
Shall we pull it together?
We shall reach out to you,
We will continue to see you.
Our generation will always
go through the bright light.
We will always make an end.
Let's just continue.
Now then, let us begin the summit meeting.
First, we'll start with a macho status
report from our national representative.
Every freaking morning
with this cleaning crap.
But thanks to you, Yuki, we
at least get to take it easy.
Quit slacking off.
Oh, come on!
Just look at that shine, will you?
Compared to your housekeeping skills,
we're just a couple of bumbling idiots.
Well, I guess I can't
really argue with you there.
Good morning!
Here come the girls
rolling in late, of course.
It is what it is.
Peaches don't grant powers to us, guys.
From day one, we're
playing life on hard mode.
Wakura!
Can you fix this for me?
Yeah, no problem.
You're always lightning fast.
Well, it's too bad it doesn't
make me popular with the ladies.
I appreciate it.
Hey, I didn't know you could sew, Yuki.
My big sister taught me how.
She said I ought to polish my skills since
guys don't get the
benefits of the peaches.
And when I didn't do it right,
she would put me in a headlock.
Poor pathetic bastard. Wait a minute.
I thought that your big
sister had taught...
Shut it.
Almost time for me to start a career.
Is this all there is?
Work a normal job and live a normal life?
No!
There has to be something
better out there.
A place where I can
actually make a difference.
How did things get this foggy?
I can't see anything.
Don't tell me this is...
Wait, am I in?
Mato?
Okay, stay calm.
Where's that instruction manual?
Here's the information
I found on Mato mishaps.
Mato refers to an alternate dimension
accessible through gateways,
also known as doors,
that may suddenly appear throughout Japan.
Injuries may be sustained as
a result of Shuki entering
our world or by civilians
accidentally wandering into Mato.
If you find yourself in Mato,
stay where you are and wait for the
demon defense force to rescue you.
Okay, then.
I just have to stay right here.
Oh.
Seriously?
Please, not here.
I don't want to die in a place like this!
A person?
You've suffered a Mato mishap, correct?
You've got to be pretty unlucky
to get attacked so quickly.
Prepare yourselves, Vile Shuki.
You're going down!
Damn it!
I knew it was too weak!
Relax.
I'm here to help.
Demon Defense Force
Commander, Kyoka Uthin.
Try to stay hidden behind me, okay?
Hey, um, things are getting
worse and worse by the second.
Hop on!
Now!
Right!
Thanks, by the way!
Don't talk.
You'll bite your tongue.
Commander!
Himari Azuma, Nei Okawabara, and Shushu
Tsuruga, 7th Squadron, reporting for duty.
Status report!
We've yet to locate any other
survivors in the vicinity.
Expand the search radius. Yes, ma 'am.
A horde of Shuki are bearing down on us
coming from our six and nine o 'clock.
Handle them for me.
I'll get this survivor to safety.
Roger.
Hey, boy.
If you want to survive,
you'd better do as you're told and
follow the commander's orders to a T.
Get out of my way!
And of all the women who've gained powers
from the peaches that
grow exclusively in Mato,
these women are the best
when it comes to combat.
The Demon Defense Force.
I've only heard rumors.
But here they are!
That takes care of that.
Is he alright?
He's unconscious, but he
doesn't have any injuries.
Nice job, Nei.
We couldn't have found him without you.
Hang in there just a little longer.
Okay, I'll try.
Man, that fight wore me out.
Stamina isn't your forte, is it?
That's funny.
The commander tells me that all the time.
Hey, do you think the commander and
that boy are back at the dorm yet?
Probably.
We can't go back yet.
We've got this kid to tend to.
Let's hurry up and get the
last sight checked out.
Sure thing.
That works for me.
Hey, Mari.
We missed out on seeing the
commander's sword skills.
An unfortunate yet necessary
evil. Oh, good. You're awake now.
You were involved in a Mato miscappant.
Where's my sister?
Hey, how did you manage to...
In the event of a Mato mishap,
victims are advised to take
the following three measures.
One, hold your breath and await rescue.
Two,
if you happen across Ashuki,
prioritize personal safety and
run as far away as possible.
And the third measure is
to keep your mouth shut.
Why did we stop?
No! Help!
No!
That's that girl!
Dodge to the right!
This thing moves too slow!
Help me!
I've erected a basic barrier.
There's no need to panic.
But...
If I was alone, it wouldn't
matter how this ends.
The Peach's gift.
Even I know I got stuck
with the lousy ability.
Sure, Kyoka's strong, but
look at what her ability is.
She'll never be Supreme Commander.
Not in a million years.
I'll show them.
I will become the Supreme Commander
in charge of all the other commanders.
I've never tested it on a man.
I always thought it'd be impractical.
I've got a decision to make.
Hey, what's your name?
I'm Wakura.
Yuki Wakura.
Yuki, in order for us to escape, there's
something I need you to do. What? Really?
I'll do whatever it takes to survive.
I like your attitude.
In that case, starting now,
you're going to be my slave.
Hello, can you give us
a little room, sweetie?
And I need you to close your eyes.
Okay, sure. Thank you.
If you have enhanced strength, we'll have
a shot at making it out of here alive.
Huh you want me to fight those things I
can't do that you said you'd do whatever!
It takes to survive
right
it's
time to
bow down then despite never even having
Touched a girl before on instinct as
if it were only logical she held out a?
a finger towards me, and I licked it.
Yuki.
Did that boy turn into
the commander's slave?
Incredible.
I didn't think it would work this well.
It's time for you to
show me what you can do!
Go, Yuki!
Jump to the left!
He's fast as lightning!
Take care of her!
You got it! Fix this! Ryota!
Commander!
That's huge!
I'll tie up the loose ends.
You and the kids take cover.
Yes, ma 'am!
Get in there, Yuki!
Use your strength and crush that thing!
Amazing!
Who the hell is he?
Where did he come from?
Where the heck did that come from?
Commander!
Head back without me.
What?
He and I need to have a conversation.
Yes, of course.
You surprised me.
I never would have
guessed you had it in you.
Perhaps we should make your job as
my slave a permanent arrangement.
A permanent slave?!
But before that, there's a caveat
to my ability we'll need to discuss.
So that's how it's going to be, huh?
What?
The price of my ability.
As the master,
I must compensate my slave
with a reward befitting
their work each time they
carry out a task. A reward?
My reward is a kiss?
You worked very hard out there.
Would you like another one?
No, no, I think I'm good.
You're the one who saved my
life, so there's no need to...
Look, I'm sorry.
I never expected something
like this to happen either.
When those Shuki were my slaves, they
were happy being paid in slices of pork.
Hey, what are you doing?
My body moves automatically regardless of
how I feel, and there's nothing I can do.
It's the price of my ability.
I'm usually indifferent
towards this type of behavior.
We successfully recovered two survivors.
Please stand by for extraction.
Roger that.
My first kiss.
Who'd have thought it
would happen in Mato?
The Shuki.
Huh?
If even one of them were to
appear in the real world,
there would be dozens of casualties.
My goal is to become Supreme
Commander of the Demon
Defense Force and exterminate
those creatures for good.
Our current commander is too lenient.
With your help, I believe I can
make the most out of my ability.
Actually, I think I'm in the
running for the position now.
Please, come work for me, Yuki.
I'm not particularly good at
stuff like sports or academics.
My housekeeping skills are the only
thing I have confidence in, but...
I'm all for a guy who knows
how to keep things clean!
But there's more to you.
You risked your life to protect that girl.
I suppose you aren't so bad for a man.
Well...
Then in that case, yes!
I want to be a hero in Mato!
Then it's settled.
Even if I get a job in the real world,
all it's waiting for me is
a life of boring mediocrity.
But in this world, I can
fight against the Shuki.
And I can avenge my big sister's death.
Plus, as long as I get my reward from
Miss Kyoka, then it will all be worth it.
This is the Demon Defense Force's dorm?
It kind of reminds me of an old-timey inn.
It was built according to Mato's
unique mystical properties.
It's also surrounded
by a powerful barrier.
This is where we deal with
all the boring red tape.
Let's head inside.
You can take a look at
your brand new workplace.
Got it.
Of course, I get to be a member of...
The Demon Defense Force.
Welcome home!
The siblings we rescued are back
home with their parents. Good.
So... who is he?
Everyone meet Yuki Wakura.
He's our new caretaker. Huh?
Huh?
Hold on a minute.
I'm the caretaker?
Of course, during combat,
you will be my slave.
But at all other times, you
will tend to the dorm's needs.
Huh?
Really?
I went to an all-girls school, so I've
never gotten a good look at a man before.
This ought to be fun.
Having a new person in the
dorm means he's Nace Jr.
But a man?
A man is gonna be our caretaker?
These girls are skilled fighters,
but they have colorful personalities.
Coupled with the Shuuki lurking about, our
caretakers don't stick around for long.
With your housekeeping expertise,
you'll be the perfect fit.
Wait, I don't get to be on
the Demon Defense Force?
Don't be ridiculous, men
aren't allowed to join.
There you have it.
Make him feel at home, okay?
If you say so, Commander.
The carpet he's tending to!
Take it out now!
I'm starving!
Make me something to eat.
Do you mind washing my uniform for me?
Slow down!
I can't work that fast!
Don't worry about it!
Nei was the last one to join
the seventh squadron before you!
As your senpai, I'm here to help!
Everything will be okay!
Oh, thanks a lot.
But, um, how old are you?
Mei is 11 years old!
She has seniority over you in the 7th
Squadron, so you better not disobey her!
Taking orders from a literal child.
Well, at any rate.
Welcome home to Mato's Elite 7th Squadron.
Thanks!
All right, let's do it.
I don't know what I can do
I'm a non-credits person
But it's just a simple
word You and the end of the
world It's going to start
with a new love For a new love
I'm so excited to be the first time I'm so
excited to see you I'm
so excited to see you
It's a new love I'm so excited
to see you I'm so excited to see
you Take my heart and put it on
and you're not ready to take it.
I'm the only one to go to the hands.
I'm the only one to hold you.
I'm the only one to keep you.
I'm not going to die.
Okay!
I'm going to talk to you about
Commander Kyoka's Peach Ability Slave!
She can use someone as her slave
for a brief period of time,
but with this ability, she's
required to give them a reward.
The Shuki's reward was well-meet.
I wonder what Mr.
Caretaker's reward is.
I'm curious. By the way,
the commander defeating
all of the Shuki with a
sword has nothing to do
with her Peach Ability.
It's the result of her
hard work and discipline.
No one else can do that.
Anyway, next time,
Curiosity Shoo Shoo Undress!